《越狱》前情提要K
Previously on Prison Break:
我要找日落旅馆的电话
I need a number for a Sundown Hotel, please,
新墨西哥州的希拉有一家
I got one in Gila, New Mexico,
NM，6-3，明天
NM, 6-3, Tomorrow,
-你是谁？ -我想你心知肚明
- Who is this? - I think you already know.
如果我把尸体埋在自家后院 我会随时挂念这件事
If I buried someone in my own backyard, I'd think about it all the time,
让我和家人消失 我会以保守你的小秘密回报你
Let me and my family disappear, And in return, I'll keep your little secret,
我知道你没料到 事情会演变成这样
It's not how you wanted this to play out,
但是有时 事情是你无法掌控的
But sometimes things happen that are just out of your control.
我们稍后见了，麦可 可能会比你想像中更快见到面
I'll see you soon, Michael, It may be sooner than you think,
-你不能来这里 -你妹妹在哪？
- You can't be here. - Where's your sister?
-我要见犸丽 -婚礼两点半就开始了
- I need to see Maricruz. - Wedding's at 2:30.
犸丽拒绝和他结婚
Maricruz, she told him no.
-你能相信吗？ -去找你的女友吧
- Do you believe that? - Go on. Get your girl.
罗杰
L.J.
-两人都趴下，现在 -拜托
- Both of you, face down. Now! - Please.
嫌犯已遭制服 疑似林克柏劳
Suspect in custody. Possible ID, Lincoln Burrows.
告诉我 你把威莫兰的钱藏在哪里
Now, you're gonna tell me where you stashed Westmoreland's money...
否则我会一针针 把你拆掉
...or I'm gonna pluck you like a chicken, stitch by stitch.
（堪萨斯州，垂比云）
你这个百万富翁的行李 还真简便
For a millionaire, you travel light.
喂，这是什么玩意？
Hey. Hey, what is this?
是量血压的器材
It's for my blood pressure.
瞧我找到什么
Lookie what I found.
看来贺兰德太太喜欢敲肉
Guess Ms. Hollander liked to beat some meat.
也许敲个几下 你就会回想起藏钱的地点
A couple whacks with this would help you remember where you put the money.
我们已经揍了他一整晚 他一声也不吭
Hey, we've been beating his ass all night. He ain't coming off the goods.
我们得换别的方法
We need to do something different.
不管你们怎么对我 我都不会说
It don't matter what you do to me. I ain't talking.
达到目的之前我不会罢手的
Well, I ain't stopping till I get what I came for.
-我们再听一次歌吧 -求求你
- How about we listen to that again? - Please.
告诉我钱在哪里 不然你就等着受死
Tell me where that money is or I'm gonna read it on your tombstone.
好，我告诉你一个线索
Okay, I will give you a little clue.
钱不在这里
It ain't here.
（FBI分局 伊利诺州芝加哥）
（林克柏劳，绰号水槽）
-已确定逮捕到柏劳 -好耶
- Confirmed. Burrows is in custody. - Yeah!
真难以置信 他竟然能到亚利桑那
Unbelievable. He made it all the way to Arizona.
再晚一天，他可能就消失了
Another day, he'd have been gone.
你找到曼宏了吗？
You find Mahone?
没有，我一直打 都转到语音信箱
No. Keep trying to call, it goes straight to voicemail.
我是亚历山大曼宏，请留言
This is Alexander Mahone, Please leave a message,
-金先生 -凯勒曼先生
- Mr, Kim, - Mr. Kellerman.
-林克柏劳已经遭到逮捕 -所以我才打给你
- Lincoln Burrows is in custody. - That's the reason I called,
-他在谁手上？ -亚利桑那州威考克警局
- Who has him? - Willcox, Arizona P, D,
必须立即把他带来
We need to extricate him, Right away,
曼宏在哪里？
Where's Mr. Mahone?
我现在正试图和他连络 不过这件事我可以处理
I'm getting in touch with him now. But I can take care of this one.
我们聘请曼宏先生是有原因的
This is why we hired Mr, Mahone,
-他是唯一的官方人士 -别担心，这件事不会正式公开
- He's the official face here. - Don't worry, this won't be official.
-也不会有人起疑心 -一定会有人起疑心
- And there won't be any questions. - Of course there will,
你要确保 没有人能活着证实那疑问
Just make sure no one's left to answer them.
（亚利桑那州，威考克）
我儿子和这件事无关，拜托你们
My son had nothing to do with this, please.
你说给法官听吧
A judge will decide that.
-你回报了吗？ -有，凤凰城派了支援
- Did you call in? - Yeah. Phoenix is sending backup.
那台车不像警察，吉米
I don't think that's one of ours, Jimmy.
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
嘿！
Hey!
快点！
Come on!
快跑K别停下
Move it! Run! Don't stop!
过来
Come here.
-放开我 -别激动K
- Let go of me. - Okay, calm down. Calm down.
-你再乱来K -你们是谁？
- You try that again... - Who are you?
我们是自己人
We're on your side.
我们是你父亲的同伙
We're with your father.
（伊利诺州，芝加哥 奥黑尔国际机场）
曼宏 林克柏劳已遭到逮捕
Mahone, Lincoln Burrows has been apprehended.
-哪里？ -亚利桑那州
- Where? - Arizona,
我正要过去 我需要你也一道去处理
I'm on my way, and I need your talents on the ground.
我有空马上会过去
I'll get there as soon as I can.
我想你没听清楚 到亚利桑那州去
I don't think you heard me. Get to Arizona.
我快找到史柯菲了
I'm this close to scofield.
我这方已经十拿九稳了
Well, we have a bird in the hand.
我这边可能也是
Yeah, well, so might I.
你不是要我找出 史柯菲和丹奎迪的集合地点吗？
You wanted me to figure out scofield's rendezvous with Tancredi?
就是在今天
It's happening today.
一切都在我的掌控之中
And I'm sitting right on top of it.
片名：越狱风云
片名：集合地点
（新墨西哥州，希拉）
（科罗拉多州，千里达）
有什么好看的？
What are you looking at?
-这是哪里？ -那不重要
- Where are we? - It doesn't matter.
你们在这很安全，请坐吧
You're safe here. You can take a seat.
见到我爸之前我什么也不做
I ain't doing a thing until I see my dad.
我只能说他正在赶来的路上 班机一小时后会降落
All I can tell you is, he's on his way. His flight lands in an hour.
我为何要信任你？小姐
Why should I trust you, lady?
我想你别无选择
I don't see you have much of a choice.
你要的话 我也可以把你交给警察
I could drop you off back with the cops if you'd prefer.
-你们还要去别的地方吗？ -的确是
- You have somewhere else to be? - Matter of fact, we do.
我们不能让你们离开
Well, we can't let you leave.
你父亲以为 你们两兄弟会在一起
Your father was expecting your brother to be with you.
知道你弟弟在哪吗？
Do you know where he is?
你真以为我会告诉你？
Do you really think I'm gonna answer that?
你必须和我们合作，林克
You need to start cooperating with us, Lincoln.
我们只是想帮忙
We're only trying to help.
麦可史柯菲
Michael scofield.
一周前从福克斯河监狱逃出来
He escaped from Fox River Penitentiary a week ago.
没有，没见过他
Nope. Never seen him.
如果见到他，请打这支电话给我
Well, if you do, please call me at that number.
好的
Will do.
再下去还有一家旅馆
There's another hotel down the road.
谢谢
Thanks.
-有事吗？ -有你的传真
- Yeah? - You got a fax.
请你从门底下塞进来好吗？
Could you put it under the door, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
（一小时后 巴特非尔路16781号）
（内布拉斯加州，戴拿索）
（联邦调查局通缉名单）
泰瑞莎，费南多苏克打电话来
Theresa. It's Fernando sucre.
-费南多 -泰瑞莎
- Fernando, - Theresa.
-她不在这里 -请别挂断，我很抱歉
- She's not here, - Please don't hang up. I'm so sorry.
拜托K
Please, just...
我只是有个问题
I just need to know something.
你现在有比我妹妹 更大的问题
You've got bigger problems than my sister right now.
等等，拜托K
No, no, wait. Please, please.
-我得跟她谈谈，拜托 -不行
- I need to talk to her. Please. - You can't,
我K我们下午就要离开了
My... We're leaving this afternoon.
-要去哪里？ -墨西哥的伊斯塔帕
- Where are you going? - Lxtapa, Mexico,
一周以后才回来
We won't be back for a week,
这原本是她和赫特的蜜月旅行
We're taking the honeymoon she had planned with Hector.
几个小时后她会来接我
She's picking me up in a few hours,
-几点？ -快两点的时候
- What time? - A little before 2.
-请她一定要打给我，好吗？ -我把号码给你
She's gonna have to call me, okay? I'll give you the number.
-你在哪里？ -打来电显示的这支号码
- Where are you? - Take this number of the caller ID,
拜托，泰瑞莎
Please, Theresa,
请她一定要打给我，好吗？
Just have her call me, okay?
我会在这等她
I'll be right here.
（此路不通）
你好，莎拉
Hello, sara.
我不确定你是否会来
I wasn't sure you'd come.
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
接下来的日子你会很难受
This isn't gonna be easy for you.
你在讯息里说 你有导正的办法
You said in your message that you had a plan to make this right.
请你告诉我是什么办法
I need to know what that is.
（日落旅馆）
有，她昨晚住进旅馆
Yeah. Yeah, she checked in last night.
-她一个人吗？ -对
- Was she alone? - Yeah.
凯莉福斯特，她住九号房
Kelli Foster. I put her in Room 9.
你是早上打给她的人？
You the guy calling this morning?
-早上有人打电话给她？ -对，他想传真给她
- A guy tried to call this morning? - Yeah, he was trying to send her a fax.
-他有传来吗？ -有，20分钟前
- Did he do it? - Yeah, 20 minutes ago.
你的传真机有记忆功能吗？
Does your fax have memory?
应该有
I guess so.
-知道这地址吗？ -离这里五分钟车程
- Do you know where that is? - It's five minutes away.
如果她回来，需要我做什么吗？
If she comes back, is there anything you want me to do?
她不会回来了
She isn't coming back.
我安排了 我们去巴拿马的计划
I've arranged for us to get to Panama.
明天我们去和我哥会合
We're meeting up with my brother tomorrow.
等等，这就是你的办法？
Wait, that's your plan?
和全美两大通缉犯 逃到巴拿马？
To run away to Panama with the two most wanted men in America?
麦可，我来这里是因为 我以为你有真正的解决办法
I came here because I thought you were gonna have real answers for me.
这就是解决的办法
This is an answer.
现在我们只有这条路可走
And right now, it's the only one we've got.
和欺骗我的男人一起远走高飞？
Running away into the sunset with the man who lied to me?
真的？你原本就知道 其他人要越狱吗？
Really? I mean, did you know about the other guys?
你知道我会让茶包这种人 重获自由吗？
Did you know that I would be putting T-Bag back out onto the street?
这不在当初的计划之中
I never meant for that to happen.
我只是不能不这么做
I was doing what I needed to do.
-不然我哥会死 -现在我爸死了
- My brother was gonna die. - Now my father's dead.
你父亲的死我很抱歉
I am sorry about your father.
我对我对待你的很多事感到抱歉
I'm sorry for a lot of things. For what I did to you.
我做了许多K
I have many...
让我后悔的事
...many regrets.
-但这件事最让我后悔 -这对我于事无补
- But that's the biggest. - That doesn't help me right now.
这点我也很抱歉
I'm sorry for that too.
我不奢望K
I didn't expect you to...
我不奢望你会原谅我
I didn't expect you to forgive me.
但是我不希望K
But I don't want you to...
我不想让你一人单打独斗
I don't want you to be alone in this.
我不想孤单一人
I don't wanna be alone.
-我们走，上车 -这头是死胡同
- Let's go. Get in the car. - We can't get out this way.
-麦可，那头是唯一的出路 -我们就往那个方向走
- Michael, that's the only way out of here. - Then that's the way we're going.
-你抓好 -麦可，你要做什么？
- Hold on. Just hold on. - Michael, what are you doing?
抓好就是了
Just hold on.
来吧
Come on.
麦可
Michael!
-你没事吧？ -他还是紧追不舍
- You all right? - He's still behind us.
坐稳了
Hold on.
站起来，包威
On your feet, Bagwell.
烤肉叉加热好了
Skewer's hot.
他有钥匙
He's got a key.
钥匙拿来，如果要我K
I'm gonna get that key if I have to...
坐下
Down.
钥匙很快就会出现，朋友
We're gonna see that key again, friend.
很快就会出现
We're gonna see it real soon.
我的信用卡还我
Give me my credit card.
你买了什么？
What did you get me?
还买了什么？
What else you get?
蜜枣汁、香烟、一点沾酱 还有一袋油腻的汉堡
Prune juice, smokes, a little dip, and a bag of sliders.
你要从哪个开始？
What do you want first?
他看起来喜欢嚼烟草
Looks like a chew guy to me.
-不准吐出来 -他的嘴含过更恶心的东西
- No spitting. - He's had worse things in his mouth.
你想要什么？费南多
What do you want, Fernando?
对未来你有何期望？
From the future?
如果我说要你，你会逃走吗？
Would you run if I said you?
如果我逃走，你会来追我吗？
Would you chase me if I did?
我们得回到我车上
We gotta get back to my car.
太远了
It's too far.
他叫更多人来之前 我们还有机会
If we go now, before he gets more people...
他不会请求支援
He's not gonna call for backup.
-他想私下解决 -为什么？
- He wants his privacy. - Why?
他不是来逮捕我的
He's not trying to catch me.
他是来取我的性命
He's trying to kill me.
你的祖父K
Your grandfather...
都是因为他我才会被陷害
...he was the reason I was set up in the first place.
他曾经替这些 想杀我的人工作
He used to work for the people who wanted me dead.
这一切都是为了引他出来
This is all just to get to him.
你父亲马上就会抵达
Your father should be arriving any minute now.
-你叫珍是吗？ 对
Jane, right?
对不起
Sorry.
没关系
Don't worry about it.
你认识我爸？
You know my dad?
很熟吗？
Well?
够熟了
Well enough.
我们曾共事过
We used to work together.
是在“公司”
The Company.
对
Yeah.
但那是很久以前的事
But that was a long time ago.
现在我和他一样 对抗“公司”
And now I work against them, just like he does.
所以你也丢下了家人 没有解释和道别
I guess you walked out on your family too. No explanations, no goodbyes.
我没有家人
I don't have a family.
林克 他真的很想见你们兄弟
He really wants to see you and your brother.
麦可十岁以后 他就没见过他了
He hasn't seen Michael since he was 10 years old.
他们到了
They're here.
在这里等
Wait here.
-我们走 -要去哪里？
- Let's go. - Where are we going?
麦可从来没见过你祖父
Michael never met your grandfather.
站住
Hey!
爸
Dad.
我不想被困在这里
I don't wanna get trapped in here.
另一头一定有出口
There's gotta be an exit on the other side.
-你先走 -麦可K
- You go on. - Michael.
我马上就来，快走
I'll be right behind you. Go.
（亚利桑那州，威考克）
坏消息，柏劳在我来之前被劫走
The news is not good. Burrows was intercepted before I got here.
对我们是一次挫败 不过还不会太迟
It is a setback, but we're not that far behind.
保罗K冷静点
Paul, Paul. Calm down.
没关系，有人会处理好
It'll be all right. Someone will take care of it.
“有人”是谁？
Someone who?
比尔，别说 你让其他人参与了这件事
Bill, tell me you're not bringing someone else in on this.
你不会以为你是唯一的大将吧？
You didn't think you were alone on this, did you?
你只是个小兵 背后还有一整个军团
You're a soldier. There's an army.
谈谈你对莎拉丹奎迪 有何发现？
Tell me, what do you have on sara Tancredi?
-她与这件事何干？ -回到你原本的任务
- What does that have to do with this? - Go back to your original assignment.
比尔，我人在这，我可以处理K
Bill, I'm here now. I can do this.
-然后K -那女孩
- And then... - The girl.
我们得查明 她父亲跟她说了什么
We need to know what her father told her,
等你查出来，再通知我
When you find out, give me a call.
我是凯勒曼探员 我要莎拉丹奎迪的租车资料
This is Agent Kellerman. I need that rental car information on sara Tancredi.
（丙烷气体）
对，就是这艘
Yeah, this is it right here,
高75尺，双柴油汽缸游艇
seventy-five foot, twin diesel Azimut...
驾驶桥楼，还有全景窗户
...fly bridge, panoramics.
只要开这种游艇，就是大人物
Pull up in a boat like that, you're somebody.
-让我看 -手拿开
- Let me see. - Hey, get off.
不要
No.
你好吗？包威
How you doing, Bagwell?
-去拿粪便 -什么粪便？
- Get the stool. - What stool?
粪便
The stool.
这是巴士站的置物柜钥匙
It's from one of them lockers in a bus station.
我会尽量不去想 钥匙是从哪里出来的
I'll try not to think about where it's been.
（911，拨号中）
-911，请问紧急状况？ -拜托别这样
- 911 operator, what's your emergency? - Don't do that. Come on.
请派警员来 有个浑蛋闯进我家
Hey there, send the police. Some scumbag broke into my house.
-地址是？ -米贝瑞山庄1605号
- Your address? - Yeah, 1605 Midberry Hill.
-他还在现场吗？ -对，你们最好快来
- Is he still there? - Yeah, you better come quick.
-走吧，罗伊 -拜托，别这么做
- Let's hit it, Roy. - Come on, now, please don't do this.
不要这样丢下我好吗？ 我带你们去找钱
Don't leave me like this. I can take you back to the money.
-我知道在哪 -我也知道
- I know right where it is. - So do I.
求你别这么做，拜托
I'm begging you, don't do this. Please.
葛瑞，来谈条件 我知道你要什么
Geary, we can make a deal. I know what you want.
不必谈条件 你最后的筹码已经没了，朋友
No deals. You just crapped out your last bargaining chip, pal.
等等，拜托
Wait, please!
如果我是你 我就不会开枪，亚历
I wouldn't do that if I were you, Alex.
闻到了吗？
You smell that?
那是丙烷
It's propane.
现在这里都是丙烷
It's filling the room.
如果你扣板机 我们会同归于尽
And if you pull that trigger, we both die.
不
No!
-我会开枪的K -也许吧
- I'll do it. I'll do it. - Maybe.
但在你开枪之前
But before you do...
我问你一个问题，亚历
...let me ask you a question, Alex.
你还认为你是好人K
Do you think you're still one of the good guys...
为正义而战吗？
...fighting the good fight?
我想我俩都清楚 你已经越过了界线
Because I think we both know you've crossed over.
你选错边站，追捕错的人
You're on the wrong side chasing the wrong guys.
我哥哥是清白的
My brother is innocent.
-他从没有杀过人 -感谢你让我看清事实
- He never killed anyone. - Well, thanks for opening my eyes.
好吧，亚历，开枪
Okay, Alex, shoot.
-下场你我都很清楚 -反正丙烷会毒死我
- We both know what'll happen. - The propane will kill me anyway.
有差别吗？ 还不如现在就死
What difference does it make? Might as well do it now.
说的有理
That's a good point.
这就好了
There you go.
这样如何K
There. There!
这样你就有时间 思考你的行为
That'll give you time to think about what you're doing.
但首先我要建议你，放弃吧
But first, a word of advice. Stop.
因为当你一接近我 我总是获胜
Because when you get close, I will win every time.
你这么想？
You think?
-现在被关的人不是我 -是没错
- I'm not the one in a cage. - No, you're not.
你和我有个很大的差异，麦可
There's one big difference between you and I, Michael.
而你刚证实了这点
And you just proved it.
你无法杀人
You can't kill.
只有杀了我，我才会放弃
And that's what it's gonna take to stop me.
因为我不像你有顾忌
Because I don't have the same reservations.
我不能有
I can't.
所以不管是今天在希拉 或是明天在阿布奎基
So whether it's today in Gila or tomorrow in Albuquerque...
或是两个月后在巴拿马
...or two months from now in Panama...
我都会逮到你
...I will get you.
我别无选择
I don't have a choice.
我替我们争取到一些时间
I bought us some time.
-你没事吧？你流血了 -走吧
- You okay? You're bleeding. - Let's go.
系好安全带
Get your seatbelt.
（堪萨斯州，垂比云）
这里，804号
Here, 804.
滚开
Move.
这真是最美丽的景象，不是吗？
Ain't that the most beautiful thing you ever seen?
一大笔钱
All that green.
比大峡谷还要壮观
It's prettier than the Grand Canyon.
罗伊，这是我俩 人生中的重要里程碑
You know, Roy, this is a monumental moment for both of us.
袋子交给我，布拉德
Hand over the bag, Bradley.
-把敲肉棒放下，老奶奶 -我可不是开玩笑的
- Put down the pounder, Grandma. - Hey, hey, I'm not kidding around.
你以为你这娘娘腔K
Oh, you think your pansy ass...?
下次你自己挖粪便吧
Next time, you pick through the crap.
好，有急救药品 抛弃式手机、两支牙刷
Okay, first-aid kit, disposable phones, a couple of toothbrushes.
汽车旅馆呢？
What about the motel?
旅馆计时收费，不检查证件
They charge by the hour, so they didn't ask for ID.
-钥匙在你手上？ -对
- Do you have the keys? - Yeah.
有带帽子吧？
Want your hat?
抱歉，我们不在家 哔声后请留言，我们会回电给你
Sorry, we're not home, Leave a message at the beep and we'll get back to you,
泰瑞莎 这通留言是给犸丽的
Theresa, this message is for Maricruz.
你打来的时候我在那里K
I was right there waiting for your call...
可是警察出现了，我不能接电话
...but the cops showed up and I couldn't pick up the phone.
我知道这大概就是 你不想和我在一起的原因
I know probably that's the exact reason why you may not wanna be with me.
听我说
Listen to me.
我的伊戴拉斯阿姨 住在墨西哥市郊
My Aunt Idalyz, she lives outside Mexico City.
在山上的牧场中 那里有骆马让孩子骑
In the mountains, on a farm, with a Ilama for the baby to ride.
所以下周，等你飞回家
So next week, when you fly back home...
回到机场的时候 我会在那里
...when you go to the airport, I'll be there.
在伊斯塔帕机场等着你
In the airport, in lxtapa, waiting for you.
我用生命向你保证
I promise you, mi vida.
宝贝，我爱你胜过全世界
I love you, Mommy. I love you more than anything.
没有你我活不下去
And I can't live without you.
我知道有办法可以解决的，宝贝
I just know I can make it work, baby.
之后如果你遇到麻烦 这会有帮助
This is in case you run into trouble down the road.
我有个办法
I have a way.
（波修伊布斯）
-她在哪里？ -谁？
- Where is she? - Who?
犸丽，她不在家也没去上班
Maricruz. She wasn't at home. She's not at work.
她不在这，我不知道她去哪里
Well, she's not here. I don't know where she is.
你想惹麻烦吗？贱人 不准骗我
You trying to cause problems for me, bitch? Don't lie to me.
她去墨西哥了，对吧？
She went to Mexico, didn't she?
（墨西哥市 伊斯塔帕）
Went on our honeymoon.
去我们的蜜月旅行
用我的钱去旅行
Paid for with my money.
待会儿一定会很痛
This isn't gonna feel good.
我很耐痛，你清楚的
I have a high tolerance for pain. You know that.
的确
You do.
你不是糖尿病患者，对吧？
And you're not a diabetic, are you?
好了
Right.
麦可，告诉我
Michael, tell me something.
你对这一切 有感到一丝丝乐趣吗？
You think there's a part of you that enjoys this?
在伤口上擦双氧水？并不有趣
Peroxide in an open wound? No.
我是指越狱
I mean escaping from prison...
过逃亡的生活 危险、恐惧、匆促、这一切
...and being on the run and the danger and the fear and the rush. All that.
这K
It...
让我觉得你在寻求刺激
It feels to me like chasing a high.
我了解那种感受K
And I know what that's like...
现在我早该学到教训了
...and I should know better by now.
我从来没这么想过
I never thought about it like that.
我知道你以前听过K
I know you've heard this before...
但不会永远这样的
...but it won't always be like this.
根据你跟我说的每件事来看 只是越来越糟
From everything you've told me, it's getting worse.
他们不可能永远追捕我们
They can't chase us forever.
今天来追我们的家伙 只能追到边境
The guy who caught up with us today stops at the border.
所以我们一定要越过边境
That's why we have to get across.
我已安排好人帮助我们
I have the people in place to help us do that.
我们明天就会去和他们会合
We're meeting them tomorrow.
再等一天，莎拉
One more day, sara.
再等一天
One more day.
这是我唯一的请求
That's all I'm asking.
去清理一下
You can go get cleaned up.
伤口保持干燥
Keep this dry.
莎拉K
Sara...
我很高兴你来了
...I'm glad you came.
那么K
So...
就是他
...this is him.
小林克
Lincoln Junior.
-用你自己的名字命名 -我不打算叫他艾度
- Named him after yourself. - I wasn't gonna name him Aldo.
罗杰
L. J...
这位是你的祖父
...this is your grandfather...
艾度柏劳
...AIdo Burrows.
嘿
Hi.
我等了好久才等到这一刻
I've waited for this for a long time.
我已替你们俩安排好 安全的落脚地
I've arranged a safe place for both of you to go to.
感谢你救我们出来
Well, thanks for bailing us out...
不过我们要去找麦可
...but we gotta meet Michael.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
边境附近 有个叫波修伊布斯的地方
Down by the border. A place called Bolshoi Booze.
-我可以单独去接他 -不行
- I can go alone and get him. - No.
情势已经变了
Things are different.
我们掌握到证据
There's some evidence.
只需要再一点时间
We just need a little more time...
我们就可以把真相公诸于世
...and we can blow this whole thing wide open.
没时间了，我信任麦可 他计划让我们逃到巴拿马
There is no time. I trust Michael. He has a plan to get us to Panama.
你不了解，林克
You don't understand, Lincoln.
你们不需要逃到巴拿马
You don't need to go to Panama.
你们不用再逃亡了
You don't need to run anymore.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
我可以单独去接他
I can go alone to get him.
-告诉我好消息 -嘿
- Tell me good news, - Hey.
柏劳一家三代都在这里
I got Burrows. The trifecta.
-把他们处理掉 -史柯菲呢？
- Take care of them, - What about scofield?
-他们要去找他 -没关系
- They're gonna meet him. - It doesn't matter,
现在就下手
Do it now.
莎拉？
Sara?
（我已经学到教训，很抱歉K）
你好啊，莎拉
Hi, sara.